freedomfastlane.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | Freedom Fast Lane: Success | Travel | Making Money | Personal Development | Extraordinary Living

## Privacy Statement

We are committed to protecting your privacy.

Authorized employees within the company on a need to know basis only use any information collected from individual customers. We will not sell, share, or rent your personal information to any third party or use your e-mail address for unsolicited mail. Any emails sent by Freedom Publishing Group will only be in connection with the provision of agreed services and products.

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Additionally, for systems administration, detecting usage patterns and troubleshooting purposes, our web servers automatically log standard access information including browser type, access times/open mail, URL requested, and referral URL. This information is not shared with third parties and is used only within Freedom Publishing Group on a need-to-know basis. Any individually identifiable information related to this data will never be used in any way different to that stated above without your explicit permission.

## Cookies

Like most interactive web Freedom Publishing Group uses cookies to enable us to retrieve user details for each visit. Cookies are used in some areas of our site to enable the functionality of this area and ease of use for those people visiting. Some of our affiliate partners may also use cookies.

## Links to this website

You may not create a link to any page of this website without our prior written consent. If you do create a link to a page of this website you do so at your own risk and the exclusions and limitations set out above will apply to your use of this website by linking to it.

## Links from this website

We do not monitor or review the content of other party’s websites which are linked to from this website. Opinions expressed or material appearing on such websites are not necessarily shared or endorsed by us and should not be regarded as the publisher of such opinions or material. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices, or content, of these sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site & to read the privacy statements of these sites. You should evaluate the security and trustworthiness of any other site connected to this site or accessed through this site yourself, before disclosing any personal information to them. Freedom Publishing Group will not accept any responsibility for any loss or damage in whatever manner, howsoever caused, resulting from your disclosure to third parties of personal information.

## Communication

Freedom Publishing Group can be contacted using the following contact information:

(866) 270-7515

PO Box 29502 #34555

Las Vegas, NV 89126
